Guide to the Henry Noble MacCracken Papers, 1907 - circa 1968
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES VII. MISCELLANEOUS WITHIN VASSAR COLLEGE, 1914-1943
  - Miscellaneous within Vassar College, 1929-1935
    - Special Lecturer on Religion (Folder 72.1)
    - Religious Conference - Dean Sperry, Apr 5 - 10, 1933 (Folder 72.2)
    - Council on Residence (Folder 72.3)
    - Residence Plan (Folder 72.4)
    - Room Assignment - New Plan (Folder 72.5)
    - Welcome to President Roosevelt, Aug 26, 1933 (Folder 72.6)
    - Russian Class (Folder 72.7)
    - Salaries (Folder 72.8)
    - Mrs. Henry Sanger (Folder 72.9)
    - Skinner Hall Dedication (Folder 72.10)
    - Social Science Research Council (Folder 72.11)
    - Smoke Nuisance (Folder 72.12)
    - Smoking (Folder 72.13)
    - Committee on Stationery (Folder 72.14)
    - Statute of Instruction (Folder 72.15)
    - Townsend Old Age Revolving Fund Pension (Folder 72.16)
    - President Taylor's Family (Folder 72.17)
    - Third Hall (Folder 72.18)
    - "Time" Magazine (Folder 72.19)
    - Trip to Southwest, March 6-21, 1933 (Folder 72.20)
    - 20th Anniversary of President MacCracken (Folder 72.21)
    - Vassar Booklet (Folder 72.22)
    - Vassar Community Church (Folder 72.23)
    - Vassar Cooperative Bookshop (Folder 72.24)
    - Vassar Foundation at Istanbul (Folder 72.25)
    - Vassar Journal of Undergraduate Studies (Folder 72.26)
    - Vassar Poetry, 1930 (Folder 72.27)
    - Vereinigung Carl Schurz E.V. (Folder 72.28)
    - Virgil Institute, 1930-31 (Folder 72.29)
    - Visas (Folder 72.30)
    - Mr. C.H. Whitaker (Folder 72.31)
    - Dean R.R. Wicks, March 1-6, 1934 (Folder 72.32)
    - Woman's College Board (Folder 72.33)
    - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom (Folder 72.34)
    - Wylie Memorial (Folder 72.35)
    - The X's, the Y's, and the Z's Song (Folder 72.36)
  - Miscellaneous within Vassar College, Aug 1935 - Aug 1937
    - American Student Union Convention (Folder 72.37)
    - American Student Union Convention (Folder 72.38)
    - Assemblies (Folder 72.39)
    - Assemblies (Folder 72.40)
    - Advertising Publicity (Folder 72.41)
    - Automobiles - Use by Students (Folder 72.42)
    - Audition (Folder 72.43)
    - Baccalaureate Preacher (Folder 72.44)
    - Broadcasting (Folder 72.45)
    - Bulletin Boards (Folder 72.46)
    - Bureau of Publication - New Direction (Folder 72.47)
    - Chapel Service Form (Folder 72.48)
    - Miss Jessie Chapin (Folder 72.49)
    - Miss Jessie Chapin (Folder 72.50)
    - Chaplain (Secretary of Religious Activities) (Folder 72.51)
    - Class Insurance (Folder 72.52)
    - Paul Cassat (Folder 72.53)
    - Comprehensive Examinations (Folder 72.54)
    - Conference on Student Life (Folder 72.55)
    - Constitution Sesquicentennial (Folder 72.56)
    - Cooperative Housing (Folder 72.57)
    - Crime Study Problem - Conference (Folder 72.58)
    - Marie Curie's Portrait (Folder 72.59)
    - Dutchess Co. Recreational Council (Folder 72.60)
    - Dutchess Junction (Folder 72.61)
    - Education - Teacher Training (Folder 72.62)
    - Education - Teacher Training (Folder 72.63)
    - Evaluation of Science Course (Folder 72.64)
    - Fingerprinting (Folder 72.65)
    - Fire Insurance - College (Folder 72.66)
    - Fire Insurance - College (Folder 72.67)
    - Gold Star Mothers of Veterans of Future Wars (Folder 72.68)
    - Graduate Fees (Folder 72.69)
    - Group Health Insurance - Faculty (Folder 72.70)
    - Celebration at University of Heidelberg (Folder 73.1)
    - "History of Vegetation of Dutchess County" (Folder 73.2)
    - Horace Festival (Folder 73.3)
    - House Libraries (Folder 73.4)
    - Housing (Folder 73.5)
    - Hymnal (Folder 73.6)
    - Institute of Student Aid (Folder 73.7)
    - Mrs. Kurt John (Folder 73.8)
    - Lighting (Folder 73.9)
    - Magazine - Publication of Quarterly (Ruth E. Campbell) (Folder 73.10)
    - Marriage and Family Life - Conferences and Lectures (Folder 73.11)
    - Mid-Year Examinations (Folder 73.12)
    - Museum (Folder 73.13)
    - National Youth Administration, 1935-1936 (Folder 73.14)
    - Night in Poland Ball (Folder 73.15)
    - Pot Luck (Folder 73.16)
    - Publishing Project - L.B. Birk (Folder 73.17)
    - Register of Funds in Trust (Folder 73.18)
    - Pushkin Centenary Celebration (Folder 73.19)
    - President's Trip to Lexington, Ky., Macon and Atlanta, Ga., Richmond, Washington, and Baltimore, Oct 17-29, 1936 (Folder 73.20)
    - Pensions - Faculty (Folder 73.21)
    - Phi Beta Kappa (Folder 73.22)
    - President's Trip, June 9-19, 1937 (Folder 73.23)
    - Parent's Conference (Folder 73.24)
    - President's Trip to Canada, Oct 25-28, 1937 (Folder 73.25)
    - President's Trip to Texas (1), Nov 19- Dec 3, 1937 (Folder 73.26)
    - President's Trip to Texas (2), Nov 19- Dec 3, 1937 (Folder 73.27)
    - President's Trip to Texas (3), Nov 19- Dec 3, 1937 (Folder 73.28)
    - Raymond Reading Room (Folder 73.29)
    - Registration (Folder 73.30)
    - A. Maude Royden (Folder 73.31)
    - Russian Class (Folder 73.32)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Henry M. Sanders (Folder 73.33)
    - National Youth Administration, 1936-1937 (Folder 73.34)
    - Scholarship Policy (Folder 73.35)
    - Religious Conferences - Dr. Kinsolving (Feb 1935) and Prof. Bixler (Apr, 1936) (Folder 73.36)
    - Social Security at Vassar College (Folder 73.37)
    - Social Science Conference (Folder 73.38)
    - Social Science Museum (Folder 73.39)
    - Songs for Founder's Day (Folder 73.40)
    - Student Assistants (Folder 73.41)
    - Student Loan Funds (Folder 73.42)
    - Survey of Religion (Folder 73.43)
    - Survey of Religion (Folder 73.44)
    - Student Reimbursement Insurance (Folder 73.45)
    - Summer School of the Theatre (Folder 73.46)
    - Taxicabs (Folder 73.47)
    - Thomas Thompson Trust (Folder 73.48)
    - Traffic (Folder 73.49)
    - Teacher's Oath Conference (Folder 74.1)
    - Teacher's Oath Conference (Folder 74.2)
    - Vassar Cooperative Bookshop (Folder 74.3)
    - Vassar Cooperative Bookshop (Folder 74.4)
    - Vassar Journal of Undergraduate Studies (Folder 74.5)
    - Vineyard Shore Schools (Folder 74.6)
    - Professor H.S. White (Folder 74.7)
    - Whitlock House (Folder 74.8)
  - Miscellaneous within Vassar College, 1938-1943
    - Academic Freedom (Folder 74.9)
    - Assembly Speech on Academic Freedom, Oct 10, 1940 (Folder 74.10)
    - Addresses - Foreign Students, etc. (Folder 74.11)
    - Alma Mater Poem (Folder 74.12)
    - Vassar Chapter, A.A.U.P. (Folder 74.13)
    - American Student Union (Folder 74.14)
    - Auditors (Folder 74.15)
    - Auditor's Report, June 30, 1937 (Folder 74.16)
    - Austen Riggs Foundation (Folder 74.17)
    - Baccalaureate Preacher (Folder 74.18)
    - Baccalaureate Service (Folder 74.19)
    - Bankers Trust Company (Folder 74.20)
    - Broadcasting (Folder 74.21)
    - Broadcasting (Folder 74.22)
    - Bulletin Boards (Folder 74.23)
    - Caldwell Portrait (Folder 74.24)
    - James H. Causey and Co. (Folder 74.25)
    - Classical Museum (Folder 74.26)
    - College Assembly (Folder 74.27)
    - Temporary Commission on the Condition of the Urban Colored Population (Folder 74.28)
    - Comparative Analysis of Budgets (Folder 74.29)
    - Comparative Income and Expenditure Study of Women's Colleges (Folder 74.30)
    - Comprehensive Examinations (Folder 74.31)
    - Comparison of Teaching Salaries (Folder 74.32)
    - Comenius Celebration (Folder 74.33)
    - Comparative Study of College Finances (Folder 74.34)
    - Czechoslovakian Emergency (Folder 74.35)
    - Deferred Annuities (Folder 74.36)
    - Dessertless Meals (Folder 74.37)
    - Episcopal Communion Service (Folder 74.38)
    - Experiment Station (Folder 74.39)
    - Faculty Pensions (Folder 74.40)
    - Family - Community Digest (Folder 74.41)
    - Mid-Year Examinations (Folder 74.42)
    - Faculty Annuities (Folder 74.43)
    - Faculty Salary Comparison (Folder 74.44)
    - Federal Art Project (Folder 74.45)
    - Beatrice T. Spencer's Fees (Folder 74.46)
    - Fees (Folder 74.47)
    - Michael Floy Diary (Folder 74.48)
    - Food Survey (Folder 74.49)
    - Form Manual (Folder 74.50)
    - Office Files (Folder 74.51)
    - Film of Vassar College (Folder 74.52)
    - Folksongs from Hudson Valley - Constance Varney (Folder 74.53)
    - Founder's Day, 1938 (Folder 74.54)
    - Founder's Day, 1940 (Folder 74.55)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (Folder 74.56)
    - Health Survey (Folder 74.57)
    - Highway By-Pass (Folder 74.58)
    - House Libraries (Folder 74.59)
    - Hymnal (Folder 74.60)
    - Hymnal (Folder 74.61)
    - Institute of General Semantics (Folder 74.62)
    - John Dewey School (Folder 74.63)
    - Margaret Lambie (Folder 74.64)
    - Laws in Relation to Negroes (Folder 74.65)
    - Lecturer in Applied Religion (Folder 74.66)
    - Claudia Lyon's House (Folder 74.67)
    - Medical Service for Employees (Folder 74.68)
    - Memorial Service for Professor Washburn (Folder 74.69)
    - Committee on Conservation of Cultural Resources of National Resources Planning Board (Folder 74.70)
    - National Youth Administration (Folder 74.71)
    - National Youth Administration (Folder 74.72)
    - New York State Historical Association (Folder 74.73)
    - Nursing School (Folder 74.74)
    - Peace Council (Folder 74.75)
    - Phi Beta Kappa (Folder 74.76)
    - "Plan for Marriage" (Folder 75.1)
    - Poison Ivy (Folder 75.2)
    - Poughkeepsie Public Forum (Folder 75.3)
    - Poughkeepsie Housing (Folder 75.4)
    - Poughkeepsie and Wappingers Falls Railway Co. (Folder 75.5)
    - President MacCracken's 25th Anniversary (Folder 75.6)
    - Miss Raymond (Folder 75.7)
    - Raymond Reading Room (Folder 75.8)
    - Reception on Feb 11, 1938 (Folder 75.9)
    - Registration (Folder 75.10)
    - Registration (Folder 75.11)
    - Registration (Folder 75.12)
    - Refugee Children (Folder 75.13)
    - Relief Appeals (Folder 75.14)
    - Religion on the Campus - Conference (Folder 75.15)
    - Religious Conference (Folder 75.16)
    - Riding Instruction (Folder 75.17)
    - Safety (Folder 75.18)
    - Scholarship for German Refugee (Folder 75.19)
    - Scholarship for Negro Student (Folder 75.20)
    - Social Science Museum (Folder 75.21)
    - Social Museum (Folder 75.22)
    - Song Contest (Folder 75.23)
    - Student Reimbursement Insurance (Folder 75.24)
    - The Statute of Instruction (Folder 75.25)
    - Summer Course in Science (Folder 75.26)
    - Vassar Summer Institute - Abstracts and Excerpts of Lectures (Folder 75.27)
    - Summer Experimental Theatre, 1938 (Folder 75.28)
    - Advisory Committee for Summer Institute (Folder 75.29)
    - Summer Institute for Family and Child Care Services (Folder 75.30)
    - Survey-Consultant Service [see "Food Survey"] (Folder 75.31)
    - Portrait of President Taylor (Folder 75.32)
    - Tennis (Folder 75.33)
    - Three-Year Plan [see also f. 75.46 Acceleration of Courses - Vassar] (Folder 75.34)
    - Use of Auditoriums by Outside Organization, 1940 (Folder 75.35)
    - Portrait of Matthew Vassar (Folder 75.36)
    - 75th Anniversary - Miscellaneous (Folder 75.37)
    - Vassar Community Church (Folder 75.38)
    - Vassar Cooperative Bookshop (Folder 75.39)
    - Vassar Journal of Undergraduate Studies (Folder 75.40)
    - Vassar Medal (Folder 75.41)
    - "Vassar Museums" (Folder 75.42)
    - Vassar Song Book (Folder 75.43)
    - Vassar's Folly (Folder 75.44)
    - Wylie House (Folder 75.45)
    - Wartime Problems - Acceleration of Courses at Vassar (Folder 75.46)
    - Wartime Problems - Course in Map-Making (Folder 75.47)
    - Wartime Problems - Blackout Regulations (Folder 75.48)
    - Wartime Problems - Agriculture - Student Help (Folder 75.49)
    - Wartime Problems - Acceleration of Courses - Students (Folder 75.50)
    - Wartime Problems - Acceleration - Miscellaneous (Folder 75.51)
    - Wartime Problems - Acceleration of Courses - Inquiries (Folder 75.52)
    - Wartime Problems - Acceleration of Courses - Discussion Meeting (Folder 75.53)
    - Wartime Problems - Positions Open to Students (Folder 75.54)
    - Wartime Problems - Coordinating Council for War Activities (Folder 75.55)
    - Wartime Problems - Defense Education (Folder 75.56)
    - Wartime Problems - Emergency Committee (Folder 75.57)
    - Wartime Problems - Emergency Council (Folder 75.58)
    - Wartime Problems - Emergency Relief Drive Committee (Folder 75.59)
    - Wartime Problems - Vassar Defense Council (Folder 75.60)
    - Wartime Problems - Committee on Emergency Use of Campus (Folder 75.61)
    - Wartime Problems - Faculty Advisers of Students on War Program (Folder 75.62)
    - Wartime Problems - Key Center in New York State (Folder 75.63)
    - Wartime Problems - Trading Post (Folder 75.64)
    - Wartime Problems - War Savings Bond (Folder 75.65)
    - Wartime Problems - Navy Department Training Course (Folder 75.66)
    - Committee for Inter-American Artistic and Intellectual Relations (Folder 75.67)
    - Institute of General Semantics (Folder 75.68)
    - International Student Service (Folder 75.69)
    - National Student Federation of America (Folder 75.70)
    - The Reverend James H. Robinson (Folder 75.71)
    - The Russian Review (Folder 75.72)
    - Tax Laws for Colleges and Universities (Folder 75.73)
  - World Youth Congress, 1938
    - World Youth Congress - Protests Pro and Con (Folder 76.1)
    - World Youth Congress Misc., July 1, 1938 (Folder 76.2)
    - World Youth Congress - Speeches (Folder 76.3)
    - World Youth Congress - Pres. MacCracken's Reports to Alumnae and Trustees (Folder 76.4)
    - World Youth Congress Misc. Reports (Folder 76.5)
    - American Youth Congress (Folder 76.6)
    - World Youth Congress - Commissions (Folder 76.7)
    - World Youth Congress - Misc. through June 30, 1938 (Folder 76.8)
    - World Youth Congress - Miss Kenyon's correspondence re petitions (Folder 76.9)
    - World Youth Congress - Miss Kenyon's correspondence re petitions (Folder 76.10)
    - World Youth Congress - Faculty Reports (Folder 76.11)
  - Radicalism - Protests
    - Radicalism Charges (Folder 76.12)
    - Mrs. Stephen Abbot - re "radicalism" (Folder 76.13)
    - Mrs. Frederick Krull (Folder 76.14)
    - Mr. Gene Tunney (Folder 76.15)
- SERIES VIII. HENRY NOBLE MacCRACKEN'S TEACHING AT VASSAR, 1919-1946
  - Dr. MacCracken's Courses
    - MacCracken's Lecture Notes (Folder 76.16)
    - Education 10b - Lecture Outlines, 1929 (Folder 76.17)
    - Education 10b, 1930 (Folder 76.18)
    - Education 10b - Bibliography, 1930 (Folder 76.18a)
    - Education 10b, 1931 (Folder 76.19)
    - Education 10b - General, 1932 (Folder 76.20)
    - Education 10b - Notes, 1932 (Folder 76.21)
    - Education 10b - General, 1933 (Folder 76.22)
    - Education 10b, 1934 (Folder 76.23)
    - Education Lectures-1935; and Misc. -1936 (Folder 76.24)
    - Education Lectures, 1937 and 1938 (Folder 76.25)
    - Education Lectures, 1941 (Folder 77.1)
    - Education Lectures, 1942 and 1943 (Folder 77.2)
    - Education Class, 1944 (Folder 77.3)
    - Education Class, 1945 and 1946 (Folder 77.4)
    - Bibliography - Education 10b (Folder 77.5)
    - Chaucer, 1929 (Folder 77.6)
    - Chaucer, 1933 (Folder 77.7)
    - Chaucer, Fall, 1933 (Folder 77.8)
    - Drama 220 (Folder 77.9)
    - Drama 255, Fall, 1934 (Folder 77.10)
    - Drama 255 (1), Fall, 1934/1935 (Folder 77.11)
    - Drama 255 (2), Fall, 1934/1935 (Folder 77.12)
    - Drama 255 (3), Fall, 1934/1935 (Folder 77.13)
    - Drama 255 (4), Fall, 1934/1935 (Folder 77.14)
    - English 245 (Folder 77.15)
    - English 255 (Folder 77.16)
    - English 260 b (Folder 77.17)
    - English 264 a and b, 1945 (Folder 77.18)
    - English 265 - Shakespeare, 1940 (Folder 77.19)
    - English 265, 1941 (Folder 77.20)
    - English 266 c (Folder 77.21)
    - Shakespeare Class - English 265 (Folder 77.22)
    - English 360 a (Folder 77.23)
    - English 368 c (Folder 77.24)
    - English 405 (Folder 77.25)
    - English 500 - Drama, 1934 (Folder 77.26)
    - English 500, 1934 (Folder 77.27)
  - Dr. MacCracken's Class in Drama, 1919/1920
    - Class in Drama, 1919/1920 (Folder 77.28)
    - Abbott, Joan (Folder 77.29)
    - Alexander, J.B. (Folder 77.30)
    - Ames, Adelaide (Folder 77.31)
    - Askew, Mary E. (Folder 77.32)
    - Bacon, Francis (Folder 77.33)
    - Baldwin, Charlotte (Folder 77.34)
    - Beale, Mary (Folder 77.35)
    - Beede, Faustina R. (Folder 77.36)
    - Barton, Faith (Folder 77.37)
    - Buffum, M.F. (Folder 77.38)
    - Burdick, Mary S. (Folder 77.39)
    - Childs, Alice M. (Folder 77.40)
    - Cowles, Harriet (Folder 78.1)
    - Dern, Mary J. (Folder 78.2)
    - Doble, Alice (Folder 78.3)
    - Doughten, Marie L.C. (Folder 78.4)
    - Drislane, Genevieve (Folder 78.5)
    - Fenton, Frances B. (Folder 78.6)
    - Folwell, Helen M. (Folder 78.7)
    - Foster, Evelyn L. (Folder 78.8)
    - Fox, D. (Folder 78.9)
    - Gallagher, Emily (Folder 78.10)
    - Haines, E. Marian (Folder 78.11)
    - Hanna, Katherine (Folder 78.12)
    - Hicks, Harriet (Folder 78.13)
    - Hooker, Emily H. (Folder 78.14)
    - Huling, Elizabeth H. (Folder 78.15)
    - Johnson, Ella G. (Folder 78.16)
    - Kaufmann, L. (Folder 78.17)
    - Lea. Elise F. (Folder 78.18)
    - Lyon, Doreen (Folder 78.19)
    - Sasse, Maria (Folder 78.20)
    - Schacht, Franziska (Folder 78.21)
    - Stern, Helen H. (Folder 78.22)
    - Stillman, Elizabeth L. (Folder 78.23)
    - Taylor, May Belle (Folder 78.24)
    - Vaughn, Olive (Folder 78.25)
    - Vinsonhaler, Frances (Folder 78.26)
    - Wasson, E.D. (Folder 78.27)
    - Whaley, Carol W. (Folder 78.28)
    - Willis, M.H. (Folder 78.29)
- SERIES IX. ASSOCIATIONS, 1915-1962
  - Associations; Schools; V.C. Publicity and Publications - Aug 1919 - Aug 1923
    - University Organizations - Questionnaire (Folder 78.30)
    - Entrance Requirements (Folder 78.31)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (Folder 78.32)
    - American Association of Collegiate Registrars (Folder 78.33)
    - American Association of University Professors (Folder 78.34)
    - American Association of University Women (Folder 78.35)
    - American College Bureau (Folder 78.36)
    - American Council on Education (Folder 78.37)
    - American Dialect Society (Folder 78.38)
    - American Philosophical Association (Folder 78.39)
    - American Psychological Association (Folder 78.40)
    - American University Union (Folder 78.41)
    - American University Union (Folder 78.42)
    - Association of American Colleges (Folder 78.43)
    - Association of Colleges and Prep. Schools of the Middle Atlantic States and Maryland (Folder 78.44)
    - Association of Colleges and Universities of New York State (Folder 78.45)
    - Association of Collegiate Alumnae (Folder 78.46)
    - C.R.B. Educational Foundation (Comm. for Relief in Belgium) (Folder 78.47)
    - Classical Conference (Folder 78.48)
    - College Conference on English (Folder 78.49)
    - Conference of Four Colleges (Folder 78.50)
    - Conference of Four Colleges - Minutes of Meetings (Folder 78.51)
    - Conference of Four Colleges - Minutes of Meetings (Folder 78.52)
    - Headmistress Association (Folder 78.53)
    - Institute of International Education (Folder 78.54)
    - Institute of International Education (Folder 78.55)
    - Institute of Politics (Folder 78.56)
    - International Federation of University Women (Folder 78.57)
    - Mathematical Associations (Folder 78.58)
    - Modern Language Association of America (Folder 78.59)
    - National Association of Teachers of English (Folder 78.60)
    - National Education Association (Folder 78.61)
    - National Research Council (Folder 78.62)
    - National University Extension Association (Folder 78.63)
    - N.Y. State Colleges, Campaigns by (Folder 78.64)
    - Publicity Campaigns by Colleges (Folder 78.65)
    - Wisconsin Colleges Associated (Folder 78.66)
    - Baldwin School (Folder 78.67)
    - Bennett School (Folder 78.68)
    - Berry School (Folder 79.1)
    - Birmingham School (Folder 79.2)
    - Margaret Booth School (Folder 79.3)
    - Bradford Academy (Folder 79.4)
    - Brearley School (Folder 79.5)
    - Calhoun Colored School (Folder 79.6)
    - The Castle School (Folder 79.7)
    - Centenary Collegiate Institute (Folder 79.8)
    - Columbia High School - South Orange, N.J. (Folder 79.9)
    - Gunnery School (Folder 79.10)
    - The Halsted School (Folder 79.11)
    - Hartridge School (Folder 79.12)
    - Hathaway- Brown School (Folder 79.13)
    - Highland Hall (Folder 79.14)
    - Hill School (Folder 79.15)
    - Hillside School (Folder 79.16)
    - Holmewood School (Folder 79.17)
    - Intermountain Institute (Folder 79.18)
    - Kent Place School (Folder 79.19)
    - Lauringburg Normal and Industrial Institute (Folder 79.20)
    - Lincoln School (Folder 79.21)
    - Mary Institute (Folder 79.22)
    - Miss Mason's School - "The Castle" (Folder 79.23)
    - Misses Masters School (Folder 79.24)
    - Mercersburg Academy (Folder 79.25)
    - Moraine Park School (Folder 79.26)
    - New Haven High School (Folder 79.27)
    - Phillips Academy (Folder 79.28)
    - Putnam Hall (Folder 79.29)
    - The Roxbury School (Folder 79.30)
    - Rutherford Public Schools (Folder 79.31)
    - St. Paul's School (Folder 79.32)
    - Miss Spence's School (Folder 79.33)
    - State Normal School (Folder 79.34)
    - The Ethel Walker School (Folder 79.35)
    - Alumnae Quarterly (Folder 79.36)
    - Miscellany Monthly (Folder 79.37)
    - Miscellany News (Folder 79.38)
    - Publicity - Mr. Johnson (Folder 79.39)
    - Vassarion (Folder 79.40)
  - Associations; Schools; V.C. Publications -Aug 1922 - Aug 1926
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (Folder 79.41)
    - American Association of University Professors (Folder 79.42)
    - American Association of University Women (Folder 79.43)
    - American Astronomical Society (Folder 79.44)
    - American College Bureau (Folder 79.45)
    - American Council on Education (Folder 79.46)
    - American Historical Association (Folder 79.47)
    - Archeologica Institute of America (Folder 79.48)
    - Association of American Colleges (Folder 79.49)
    - Association of Colleges and Preparatory Schools (Folder 79.50)
    - Association to Aid Scientific Research by Women (Folder 79.51)
    - Bureau of Vocational Information (Folder 79.52)
    - Classical Associations (Folder 79.53)
    - Confederation Internationale des Estudiants (Folder 79.54)
    - Conference of Four Colleges (Folder 79.55)
    - Conference of Four Colleges - Minutes (Folder 79.56)
    - Continental Pedagogical Congress (Folder 79.57)
    - Cooperative Bureau for Women Teachers (Folder 79.58)
    - Educational Aid Society (Folder 79.59)
    - Institute of Historical Research (Folder 79.60)
    - Institute of International Education (Folder 79.61)
    - Institute of International Education (Folder 79.62)
    - Institute of International Education (Folder 79.63)
    - Institute of Politics (Folder 79.64)
    - Mathematical Association of America - American Mathematical Society (Folder 79.65)
    - Modern Language Association (Folder 79.66)
    - National Education Association (Folder 79.67)
    - National Research Council (Folder 79.68)
    - New York Library Association (Folder 79.69)
    - Albany Academy for Girls (Folder 79.70)
    - Avon Junior College (Folder 79.71)
    - The Baldwin School (Folder 79.72)
    - The Bennett School (Folder 79.73)
    - Bradford Academy (Folder 79.74)
    - Bradford Academy (Folder 79.75)
    - Katherine Branson School (Folder 79.76)
    - Brearley School (Folder 79.77)
    - Colonial School for Girls, Washington, D.C. (Folder 79.78)
    - Columbus School for Girls (Folder 79.79)
    - Dana Hall (Folder 79.80)
    - Ely School (Folder 79.81)
    - Ethical Culture School (Folder 79.82)